[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie The Hunt for Red October, the Red October set sail from what Soviet port?", "correct_answer": "Murmansk", "incorrect_answers": ["Sevastopol", "Vladivostok", "St. Petersburg"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of woman stands behind every great man according to Bruce Almighty from the self-titled movie?", "correct_answer": "A woman rolling her eyes", "incorrect_answers": ["A blonde blushing woman", "A woman who is ready to give up her life for him", "A woman saying \u2018Don\u2019t say that on TV, honey!\u2019"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How permeable is the cell membrane?", "correct_answer": "It is semi permeable", "incorrect_answers": ["It varies in permeablity", "It is fully permeable", "It is not permeable"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is TRUE about pandas?", "correct_answer": "They are carnivores.", "incorrect_answers": ["They belong to the raccoon family.", "They are poor climbers.", "They were unknown to the Western world until the 1600s."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to the genre rules, what is the only sure way to kill a zombie?", "correct_answer": "Cut its head off", "incorrect_answers": ["Shoot it with a silver bullet", "Stab it in the chest", "Cut its limbs off"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the supposed reason for Charles Darwins health problems that started in 1837?", "correct_answer": "Overwork", "incorrect_answers": ["Allergy", "Depression", "A mysterious disease that he caught during his first voyage"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All starfish have 5 arms.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many species of skunk exist?", "correct_answer": "11", "incorrect_answers": ["6", "8", "13"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The stonefish is an extremely venomous type of fish that lives in the coastal regions of Indo-Pacific oceans. How does it inject its venom?", "correct_answer": "With its dorsal fin", "incorrect_answers": ["With its sharp teeth", "With its tail fin", "With its pectoral fin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these bands is featured on the soundtrack of the Transformers 2 movie?", "correct_answer": "Linkin Park", "incorrect_answers": ["Evanescence", "Rammstein", "Metallica"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is the name of one of The Three Stooges?", "correct_answer": "Moe", "incorrect_answers": ["Sep", "Ham", "Lou"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the average incubation period of crocodile eggs?", "correct_answer": "80 days", "incorrect_answers": ["50 days", "120 days", "25 days"]}]